Will you eat too?  I have brought it also.
Will you eat?   Can you
show this?
Someone is showing the man.
Oh brother, I ate it.
something is happening?   It is there and there.
What happened?
Good morning guys.  Welcome to my new
blog.  So brother, look everyone is eating food here.
And Kunali is having fun.  Kunali is
not eating food.  Kunal is eating only
ice cream.  He filled it with so much and finished it too.
Look, he is also happily watching his TV.
So this is the real fun
in life.  We are eating pulao and
chutney here.  And look, he is
filling his stomach with just ice cream.   It is
tasty.
How do you feel in such a life?
Feels good.
We
wow.
Taking out the entire box.  Please.   I
even finished the box.   I
kept the same from now on.   He
wants this sweet like chocolate, no what else, he was
drinking Jaljeera just now, he
drank the bottle of Jaljeera
and he has also made his right on the TV,
eat as much food as he wants, after this what I am going to feed you,
you will be stunned after eating it, you will
eat Chip Jo Chip,
oh yes, I keep telling you about this, it will be
better, not Puri, I am going to
feed you one more thing,
Jo Chocolate
Jo Chocolate, the spiciest chocolate, I am going to
save this one
and feed it to everyone, the entire family, listen everyone.  We will
take reactions from all those who are going to do the chip challenge and see how they feel.   There is
chilli in it.
Hain
Mirchi
Kunali Nice View.
Nice view.
Your letterbox is open.
Stop him.
Hey Chi hey
I don't wear septum.
Come on brother, let's start today's challenge.
Look, I have a Jojo chip in my hand and there is also a new
thing.  Which is Jo Chocolate Bhai, the
spiciest chocolate in the world, so we are going to
try this also.  I have
not even tried this till date.  So Kunal
Ready, what would you like to eat first?
Jolo Chip
Jolo Chip Chalo, have you ever eaten it till date?
Never eaten?   Here you go,
unbox it and try it.   Let's
see how Kunalu feels.   I have to
eat.
Yes, yes I want to eat.   It is
bursting.
Look brother, it has opened.  Look, this is what's inside it.
[Sound of deep breathing]
Look,
you will also eat it today, I have brought it too, you will
eat it, you can eat it, you
can try it,
show me how it
looks,
then
open it and show me how it looks, take it out once and take it out
properly, it should not break, guys,
even mother is saying that I will try it, right now
I will lick my finger, the crisp is saved,
yes no friend I am
scared, I will eat the crisp, not too much, no, I have to
eat it crisply,
oh take it like this, eat it like this, let's go, there is
some chilli in it,
eat it yourself, then
eat it first, no no,
first Kunali will eat it brother, the crisp
lips are looking dull, wait wait,
just one minute, what is
red chilli in it, what are you
going to take, one minute,
ok, I am going to take ice cream, let's keep it here,
guys.  Safety First: I have
seen many people getting scared, they feel very scared of the chillies
and they don't have any water or anything for two minutes after eating it.   Are you
crazy?  Crazy what a
deal?
Eat it, why are you making so much drama?   It
seems to be real.  I am not lying.
I am not lying.   If it
is Kunali then it is like chips.  Will anything happen?  It will just feel
spicy if it feels spicy.  And what else is there, it's not just
chips,
Amma, look, you will eat it, you will eat it,
Dada, what should I do, cut it,
Amma is saying, I don't have any teeth, with
whom will I eat, I have proper teeth, I have three, it's not the
lower ones, otherwise I will cut it,
eat quickly, I have to eat too much, don't
eat less,
yes, come on, eat, I can't eat, friend, yes,
by the way, he says, I am this, I am that, I have killed him, isn't he
your man,
yes, he is a man, he is
not even showing off like this, a man,
oh brother, he has eaten,
and this is how it happens, hey, don't run, don't run, stop, stop,
running like this is causing some damage to the chilli,
eat too much
[sudden heavy breathing sound] [sudden breathing sound] there is
water in it, there is
so much chilli in it,
now you try it, then how much
is there, this is how many
pieces,
one piece is there, that's all
I like it very much, how many
chilli is there, how many was there,
my father,
how was your first experience,
experience [laughs] I
still have to eat chocolate, I still have to
eat chocolate, I still have to
eat chocolate, have you seen it yet  He was saying, will you
try now, will you still try, wo
n't you try, my friend,
Amma is there.  Amma is dangerous.  Let's let Amma
try it.  First
look at that, Kunal's condition has worsened
brother.  Let's let Amma also experience it.
Amma is saying that I will eat it.   Please
eat something for me.
[nasal sound] Let's
see straight away Amma quickly.
[suddenly loud breathing sound]
That's such a relationship.  What shall I do?   Are you
feeling it?
And here it is.
What is?
what a laugh?   The
poison is there.
Yes, he
says
in the fire,
okay,
hey friend,
what happened?
What happened Amma, Amma's condition worsened
?
[laughter] It got
weird.  Hey strange father,
tell me now.
Now speak.
[laughter]
What happened?   It is
too much, yes it is, it is
poison, poison, not soil,
come, my stomach is
upset,
what happened, it feels strange, let
mom try it,
see, I have crushed chillies, it is
chillies, what
happened, what happened, what kind of a
child is this [laughs],
what happened?   It
's fast, bae.  It is very fast.
What is this?   I went and got it.   Oh my god,
smoke is coming out of my ears and nose.
[laughs]
Let's go to Avantika.   Then
why?
No.
What happened?  Tears came to my eyes.
Brother, mother brought sugar.   I am a
little bit lazy.   I have to
bring such a thing.   Oh my god,
what is it?
More is happening.
Come on brother, I have given everyone the experience of Jo
Chip.  Everyone's condition has worsened.  Look at this.
So now it's the turn
of chocolate.  Hottest Chocolate.
Hottest Chocolate.
Hey, this looks like a bean to me.  Is it chocolate
or chips?   It's just
beans.  Show it like this.
Come on, open it and show me.  It will open from here.  Look,
this has to be opened here.  I opened it from here.
Oh
guys, this is chocolate.
Dude, it smells really good like chocolate.
[nasal noise]
What happened?  It is not spicy.  Sure.
Now is it a little painful
or not?
Not much.   Do
n't eat anymore brother.
Not much.
I have never tried this till date.
So I will try this too.
The bag seems smaller in this since then.  Meaning it
seems a little sharp right now.
Brother, it is looking good.
I am
feeling it.  How did you not like it?   Don't know.
He must be getting the taste of that first.
One,
two, three actions
seem to be happening or
not.
[laughter] There
's water here.
[laughter]
[sound of deep breathing]
better than before, you won't be scared, you will eat it in one go,
I am sure of that
[sound of clearing throat] have
you all ever tried it,
no, come on,
eat this one for the first time today, yes nothing happened, nothing happened,
who came, give him
two waters,
[sound of clearing throat] [laughter] it is happening, it is happening,
but I,
but I will bear it,
so Kunali wins this challenge because
Kunali has eaten the most, brother, I
even ate chocolate after that, it is happening
now, friend,
now take the water, keep it,
drink it, keep
one packet at home,
we will tell you, it happens,
anything happens, as if he had an attack,
what are you saying, it is a
small thing, feed him chicken.
I am saying the same thing.  This is good.   Give
him this much.   You may be a
little paralyzed.
what is from?  Blood circulation is created.
Sweating Guys,
just came to the studio.  And
look at the studio today, we're putting up
all our art wax.  Look, all these have
just been kept down here.  And look at Avantika
brother.  Avantika is painting.
Excellent.  Guy Orio also came
to the studio.  Brother, look how the weather has become.  It
seems like it is about to get dark while it
is still daytime.
Brother, the weather is very dangerous and look, such a
strong storm is blowing.  It all fell apart.
All the people hanging clothes fell down.  And you can
fall down from here also.  Look, if
someone goes down from here, look, the mums are sitting down
there.  Guys, now see Avantika is going to be very
happy.  Because
I have put up the painting he made here in the studio.
See.
What happened?  Wow what?   It has come, friend.
I emptied it completely.
Yes, I understood, that's why you called me. I have my
eyes on my painting for me, that's why you
called me. You are
calling me like this. Come, come quickly, I
want to ask. I said, till date you have never asked me what to
keep where. You are about to
reach like this, what will you ask me like this.
Good morning Piyush, wake up guys. It is about to be
morning for Piyush. Should I show you the time, it is already
7:00 in the evening, guys.   No, no,
with the evening,
yes, with his morning, guys, with
our evening and with Piyush's morning,
today there is a difference between AM and PM, yes, there is a
difference between AM and PM.
Piyush ji can get up now.  It is good to be together
anyway.  Isn't it?
Yes.
What do you say?
Yes, breathing is fine.
Piyush is living in a different world, guys.
Guys are for content, right?  Yes, there is
content in sleeping as well, if I had
woken up,
yes, there is content even then, and if I had woken up early in the morning, there is
content and if I had woken up late, then there is
content only, guys, it is
money only [laughs], do
n't you feel scared, see what is there next to you
brother, if you suddenly wake up in the
dark at night, if you see this, guys, right now we have
dinner, potato-cabbage roti, raita and
chutney,
see this also, and the clothes will not fit, the
body will become so thin, one
must eat food, what happens if one
eats roti,
and what happens without roti, nothing happens, whatever you
say, I will leave roti, I
should eat, isn't it, mom,
and that is not it,
son, this is the age, if she does not eat, then how will she do it in the
future, I told you this, you are
seeing the situation, I did not
tell you this, friend, this is wrong,
wrong, friend, what else,
you are five years old, do
not eat from now on,
this is the food, this is Avantika's
paneer, nowadays children do not have to eat food,
roti, she will
not eat, and see, he is not eating outside during the day,
how many vegetables have he taken, he eats only one spoon of
rice even during the day  Yes, you have stopped him from
eating,
why would I stop him from eating, friend, if my
stomach is upset then it is okay if I don't
eat, I will become fat, hey,
you come with me to the gym tomorrow, do gym, it is
good, it will not happen if my son does not eat,
friend.   There is a
same scene of Kunal Kunal and Avantika in the guys house.  Kunali does
n't eat, Avantika also doesn't eat.  Both do
not eat.   Should be.
Food should not be like this.
Clothes do not judge a very weak man.
How many were worn
and what?  There must be some.  Should
be good.  What is that?   Are
you okay?
Yes correct.   To
take my own.
My leg would not have been broken.  I would have been
better.
Back ache, the waist was already broken,
then the leg broke, then the heart broke, then
what, old,
then you have become old, you have become old, it has been so many years for
me, then I have
reduced to 73 years,
then I have grown old, son, I have grown old, still
I am
walking a lot,
tell me, one should eat like this, look, I have become so heavy,
look, I am filling up with
vegetables, I am
filling the leaves outside
[laughs] one
should eat more,
look, we have
come in this way in life, there is food to eat, what else is there, what else are we eating, this is what has
happened, roti, chaav
and what else are we eating, this is what has happened
outside,
this is our vitamin, vitamin C, vitamins,
all these are
[laughs]
vitamins, do you
know what have you brought, whatever you brought
in school,
best, hey, what was this
?
Power of the hydrojeep.
What was this?   There was
power of the hydrojeep.
Guys Jaloji, you
know there is fire coming out from the backyard.
What is your son learning later?
What all did you do?
Kunali?  What did you do just now?
What?  What did you do?
You just check it out now.  See it in Vogue.  When
Vogue comes, then you will see what he has done, I will
tell you now, then you will not be able to eat food, I
cannot tell you while eating food, you
tell me
brother, bring the puja plate, friend, the puja
plate
Om Jai Shrita,
such
utensils go in dense utensils, you would have a fight,
yes, right now your mother will stand up.   Do
not do it.
When will you bring it?
Modi ji had left the utensils empty.
Wow!
This is it.  Look like this.
How are you feeling in 11th class?
Is good.  I am having fun.
10th was good, 11th is good?
11th is great.   Yes
?  Enjoying studying commerce?
Yes.
Come on brother.  I should enjoy it.   I am having
fun.   You
slept in school, right?   Did
n't we sleep in school?   a
little.   You must have
slept a little, right?  One player each.   I
slept in school also.  Hey, it was a free period,
what could I do?
Well, I
slept
brother, the
10th result has not come yet.
Oh yes, the 10th result has not come yet.   Will
come in May.
When will it come?
Who is saying May?   The
result comes in May.
When will it come?
I am saying.   It will
come on 15-20 June.   The
result comes in April or May.
15-20 is coming.
15-20
Hey it's coming in 15-20.
Everyone's is different, right?  His must be coming soon.   Must be
coming soon.   You are
telling me your time.
You are telling me about the marriage of your time, did you
even ask for a girl, did no one come last time,
no,
whatever it is, it is good, he
failed in his physical, right, his PC will work again,
why should he fail,
anyone can fail, so I
hope you liked today's vlog, if you
liked it then like it and subscribe to the channel, we will meet
in the next vlog, thank you so much for watching
[Sangeet]
aa [
Sangeet]